<?xml version="1.0"?>
<html display_name="edx4edx Course">
  <body>
    <h1>Introduction</h1>
    <p>
edX4edX introduces the edX course system from an authoring standpoint, detailing its motivations and general components.
Complete with videos, E-text, assessment problems, and interactive and intuitive tutorials, edX4edX provides potential
authors the necessary skills to build or edit an edX course.
</p>
    <h1>edX Content</h1>
    <p>
      <span>An edX course consists of three principle content components:</span>
    </p>
    <ol>
      <li><span>Video snippets</span><span> collection </span> - Each video snippet is less than 10 minutes long and is integrated with other course content. 
</li>
      <li><span>Assessment problems</span> - Interactive questions presented to students. There may be about 80 problems assigned for a typical 14-week semester long course. 
</li>
      <li><span>E-text</span><span> </span> - Content may be pages from a textbook, presented as images or web-formatted content with links.  E-text is also interwoven with video and assessment problems.
</li>
    </ol>
    <p>
      <span/>
    </p>
    <p>
      <span>
        <h1>Additional Course Components</h1>
        <style type="text/css">li {list-style:circle; }</style>
        <p class="c0">
          <span>Building on the course content, the edX system provides:</span>
        </p>
        <p class="c0 c6">
          <span/>
        </p>
        <ol class="c9" start="1">
          <li class="c1 c0"><span>A discussion forum for students and instructors </span> - The discussion forum is loosely moderated, and encourages students to answer each other&#x2019;s questions.  It is based on the &#x201C;askbot&#x201D; system, in which good answers are voted up, and common questions can be merged together into a single discussion thread.</li>
          <li class="c0 c1"><span>A course wiki </span> - The course wiki is open to student-authored content, and typically contains reference material and links amplifying course-provided content.</li>
          <li class="c1 c0"><span>Performance tracking </span> - The performance tracking system records student progress and grades.</li>
        </ol>
      </span>
    </p>
    <p class="c0">

</p>
    <h1>edX4edX Course Goals</h1>
    <p>The goal of edX4edX is two-fold. First, to explain the
capabilities and limitations of the courseware prototype.
Second, to gather inspiration and pedagogical data on online teaching
from instructors that have run existing edX courses, and to present those to future instructors.

<style type="text/css">li {list-style:circle; }</style></p>
    <p class="c0">
      <span>By the end of this course, you should be able to understand, edit, and author:</span>
    </p>
    <ol class="c9" start="1">
      <li class="c8 c0">
        <span>CourseContent &#x2013; the top-level document specifying the structure and organization of an edX course.<br/></span>
      </li>
      <li class="c8 c0">
        <span>E-text &#x2013; the &#x201C;textbook&#x201D; content associated with an edX course<br/></span>
      </li>
      <li class="c8 c0">
        <span>Video &#x2013; the edX video player system</span>
      </li>
      <li class="c8 c0">
        <span>CapaProblems &#x2013; Assessment problems, which are loosely based on the LON-CAPA concept</span>
      </li>
    </ol>
  </body>
</html>
